Hello, boys!
Everyone's here working hard, I see.
Today, I have someone lovely...
to introduce to all of you.
This is our new intern
in my department.
Hello, I'm Jomkaen. Please take good care of me.
Jomkaen...
Don't worry. Working here with us,
we treat each other like family—very chill and relaxed.
Looks cute.
Yes.
Uh... Jomkaen said it's cute. Ah... we're cute, too.
Sitting around like a cute family.
Uh...
Boss?
Yes?
I think the big boss was looking for you just now.
Khun Ton.
Yes?
Yes.
How are you?
Doing good.
How have you been?
Glad we're interning at the same place, Pond.
EP.10 Loop
I'm here to hand in the Team Building report, Khun Ton.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I saw my brother's story.
I don't hold a prejudice against you.
But...
I don't think
you truly love my brother.
I really like Tontae, Khun Ton.
When I'm with Tontae, I feel really good.
And I think
if we officially date,
it will be even better, Khun Ton.
That's such a childish way of thinking.
And have you ever wondered
if my brother truly loves you?
Or is he
just using you
to replace someone else?
Now about work, Khun Best.
You're very capable.
Yes.
You know how to conduct yourself. You're smart.
And I believe you know how to find ways
to benefit yourself quite well.
I've never intended to take advantage of your brother.
I only just found out that your brother
is Tontae.
Prove it then.
Why don't you prove it?
How about increasing your KPI targets by 50%?
And that applies to every single metric.
Every single metric, Khun Ton?
Also, during this time,
I don't think the two of you should see each other.
How does that sound?
What if Tontae comes to stay with me?
You shouldn't forbid him.
You're truly in love, right?
Both you and my brother.
In the meantime, stay away from each other.
I don't think I can stop Tontae.
Then make sure you do.
If your love is genuine,
or are you just using my brother for personal gain?
Alright. I'll make sure to do it, Khun Ton.
Okay. That's all I wanted to talk to you about.
You may get back to work.
Um...
Actually, I have one question I'd like to ask you, Khun Ton.
Sure, go ahead.
Are the two of you really biological brothers?
If you really want to know,
we'd have to go back to my father's time.
Best!
Did you adjust the KPIs?
You just adjusted them at the beginning of the year.
It's almost year-end, and you bump them up another 50%? Who can do that?!
We can.
It's time you helped me out, Dan.
Help with what the hell?
50% in 6 months! Who on earth can achieve that?
What do you expect us to do, work 80 hours a day?
I don't know.
I just have to pull it off.
If I can't... I'd probably...
What?
If you fail, you...
You're acting as if
if you fail, you'll have to break up with Tontae.
Well, Tontae is Khun Ton's brother.
Huh?
That's the thing.
Khun Ton called me in to talk,
forbidding me from dating his brother
unless I hit these targets.
My god... I get it now.
But what crazy person mixes personal stuff with work this much?
I think
he wants to test
whether I can truly take care of his brother.
And I also want to know
if Tontae truly loves me.
I thought Pond was dramatic enough,
but are you living in a vertical web drama or something?
I'm serious, Dan.
Yeah, fine...
As for work, you and I just have to push through.
So how are you going to tell Tontae?
You're going to disappear completely like this.
Will you even have time to see him?
I'll probably just let it slide.
I'll just fade away.
Without saying anything?
Are you really going to pull off a cold ghosting routine
and just walk away without telling him anything?
I wish I could just walk away easily, too.
Yeah, that's gonna be tough.
Really tough.
Yay! You're back, Best.
Why are you waiting here?
Well,
I was waiting for you
so we could go back together.
Do you wait like this every day?
Yes.
Ton...
Yeah?
From now on, you don't need to wait for me anymore.
What's wrong with you?
Where are you going?
Kaen and someone from the department invited me to a movie.
Kaen likes the same movie genre as me, too.
Besides, it premieres today, so I'm scared my friends will spoil it for me.
Kaen?
What?
Don't you want me to go?
If you want to spend time with me, just say so.
No... I just want to eat.
You miss my home cooking, don't you?
Am I right?
Hold on a sec.
Hello?
Hey, I won't be able to make it after all.
Suddenly, my heart started racing...
Hear that?
Oh.
I think I'll stay in my room.
Sorry about that!
Did you really just ditch your friend like that?
Well, I'd rather stay here with you.
Don't you want to be with me?
Go cook then.
Come make it with me.
I really love it
when you want me around.
Didn't it occur to you that I was just hungry?
Keep playing tough all you want.
Who are you texting?
Best.
Hey...
What's the deal between those two?
Ton said Best has been indifferent to him.
How about saving yourself first?
And how am I supposed to save myself from you?
Are you not going to give it a rest at all?
I could go all day like this.
Whoa...
Ugh, I don't want to watch this anymore.
Huh?
If you love her, why let her go?
Maybe he has his reasons.
Just because the female lead is plain,
messy-haired,
wears glasses,
and looks nerdy...
And then she gets insecure, thinking she's not good enough for him.
Did she even ask him
if he was actually okay with it?
Ow... My neck hurts so bad.
My whole body aches.
Since my whole body aches, can I just sleep here?
Then don't sleep.
But I want to sleep with you.
Ouch!
Do I look like a bed to you?
That hurt!
You have to take responsibility for me.
And how exactly am I supposed to do that?
By letting me sleep on the sofa with you.
If you want to sleep, just sleep.
I'm leaving.
Dan, that's my room!
If you're going to sleep there, you have to let me sleep, too!
Is there anything I can help you with? I want to help.
Let me work for a bit, okay?
Hey... What kind of work are you doing?
Let me see!
Best...
Ever since we came back, you've seemed stressed.
Is something wrong?
I just have a few things on my mind.
Can I help? I can help you out.
Then...
Could you give me some time?
Are you messing with me right now?
I just want us
to take a break for a while. Can we?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Since coming back from out of town,
you've been giving me the silent treatment for 3 to 4 days.
And today, when we finally spend time together,
you tell me to take a break?!
Just taking a break for a while.
How long is "a while"?
How many days?!
I just...
want to think over whether we can really be together.
Are you not sure if I want to be with you?
Or are you not sure if YOU want to be with ME?
That's not it, Ton.
I just wanted to...
I'm really hurt, you know?
I'm going upstairs to cry.
Do you hear me? I'm going upstairs to cry now!
And I'm going to cry really out loud!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Share your thoughts on the series "New Boyfriend".
Leave your impression in the comments below this video
and share it to any of your social media accounts.
Don't forget to tag #NewBoyfriend #NewBoyfriendTheSeries
The 2 most impressive comments selected by our team
will receive official series souvenirs every week!